Contact

+34 677 77 97 09 (Mobile) patrickminerovalencia@gmail .com

www.linkedin.com/in/patrick-minero-valencia (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Spanish Italian Team Leadership

Patrick Minero

Customer Service Professional

Barcelona, Catalonia, Spain

Summary

I am a Customer Service professional with over 10 years of experience in the food and retail industries. I like challenges and I love to take on responsibilities, this helped me gain skills to climb positions from dishwasher all the way to management,

I am in constant learning, improving and getting new professional and personal skills.

Experience

Joinery California
Restaurant Supervisor
May 2017 - April 2018 (1 year)
Sausalito, California, United States

I helped the General Manager with opening and closing procedures, balancing daily cash deposit, service and product training for new staff. I was responsible to provide staff with everything they needed to handle a work load of up to 400 guest a day while providing the best experience possible.

Mill Valley Beerworks
Team Lead
September 2015 - April 2018 (2 years 8 months)
Mill Valley, California, United States

This was a dual position as I was the Team Lead but also had to be part of the Server staff. I was responsible for opening procedures, provide the best experience for our guest and guarantee every staff member provided the same quality of service all while keeping our check average over USD 40 as it was the restaurant's goal.

I was also responsible to balance out the cash deposit at the end of the shift as well to make sure the restaurant was in pristine conditions for the next day. Provided service and product training for new staff members

Equator Coffees Cafe Manager

May 2013 - January 2015 (1 year 9 months)

Mill Valley, California, United States

This was the first retail cafe for the coffee roasting company.

I was responsible for labor, payroll, inventory and finances management for the cafe. I was in charge of the first tier hiring process as well as training and product knowledge. After hard work and incredible team effort, the store was able to surpass the store projections, this lead to what is now one of the Bay Area's best coffee retailers.

La Boulange Cafe & Bakery
Assistant Manager
February 2009 - March 2012 (3 years 2 months)
Novato, California, United States

This was my first restaurant job. I started as a dishwasher/prep cook for the morning shift and finished as the assistant manager. My everyday responsibilities on top of normal cleaning and cooking when necessary included hiring , payroll, finances, team building, staff training and ordering and inventory management.

Education

College of Marin

General Studies · (2009 - 2010)

Universidad Centroamericana José Simeón Cañas El Salvador Law (2005 - 2007)